Noon tomorrow.
A visitor will be coming to see you.
But you must not meet them.
No matter what, you absolutely
cannot go to the visiting room.
There's a visitor for you.
Abandon this visit and
go back to your cell.
Old man.
John Gloria.
He's the one who plotted everything.
In other words, John Gloria is
most definitely a stand user.
All you need to understand is that
you're being targeted right now.
I'll get you out of here immediately.
The handcuffs.
When did they...
Jolene!
Get away from that door now!
Now!
Star Platinum! The world!
Time, stop!
What the fuck?
Did I just get shot? Don't move.
He's begun his assault.
So it was reacting to the air currents
in order to predict our location.
Don't move until we know
the mechanism of the Snipes.
We clear?
Don't order me around
like I'm a stupid child!
I know all that already.
F...
F-E-40536.
Who do you think you're
talking to, you bitch?!
Jolene!
Are you... Don't move.
And be sure not to raise your voice.
It will keep scouting our location.
John Gloria is able to read the
flow of air with that thing.
It could even be able to react
to mild changes in our breathing.
In that stand is his satellite.
His sniping satellite.
Where he aims his rifle at the stand,
which then redirects the bullet.
John Gloria is in the men's prison.
There's no way we can
attack him from this room.
So instead, we have to
smash his satellite stand.
Because any damage inflicted on the stand
is passed through to the user as well.
Yeah, I know.
But the problem is, when
we move to strike it,
the change in the air current
will give him our locations,
and he'll attack us immediately.
Don't move away from the wall, Jolene!
It's actively hunting you!
Sholeen, what are you doing?
I'm not going to kill you.
I'm not going to die.
OK.
All right.
Not for survival day. Get away. Go.
I don't wanna say.
Let's go.
Come and find a way.
I'm on me.
Break out.
Keep up.
I can hardly afford to
place my faith in muscles.
When the skin is exposed to the wind,
muscles become stressed and cause
subtle expansions and contractions.
These minor movements are ones
that the body cannot control.
I support the rifle with bone.
The bone embraces the certainty of the
ground and the gun unifies with it.
I place my trust in that stability.
Meteorologists say wind movements are
unpredictable and they have a point.
But that doesn't mean it's impossible.
Is this fly simply?
buzzing around aimlessly in space.
Hardly, this fly is guided by the
smell and flow of the air as it flies?
for the wind is the movement of the fly.
Just as the guard said,
Jotaro Kujo has appeared.
He's here visiting his
daughter, Jolene Kujo.
Which means two bearers of the Joestar
bloodline are in that visiting room?
placing them within range
of my downtown transfer.
Joestar, Joestar, Joestar, Joestar!
When I've finally erased your legacy,
only then will my life truly begin.
At last, I will exact my vengeance for
you robbing me of my heart's support.
I see.
You said we needed to take
this thing out, is that right?
Watch it.
The droplets are making it move erratically
because it can't detect the airflow.
Now!
Down ocean!
Wait!
Jolene, look closer!
It's dodging the drops
of water one by one.
It's reading the shifts in the
air current caused by the drops.
Jolene, get back to the
wall before it shoots you!
Well, this blows.
Once the guards get here, the
air will all shift at once.
Jolene, you must listen!
Huh?
Hurry!
You have to move the stone block
at the bottom of the pillar!
Hit it with all you've got!
You again?
Don't worry about me!
Just do it!
Got it?
Don't forget what I told you!
I want you to make it through this!
I have no idea what's going on,
but this hole here between
the walls leads down there.
It's some kind of passageway.
Perhaps into the prison
sewers or through a vent.
Where the hell does it go?
For all we know, it could lead outside.
Let's go, Jolene.
We haven't got a choice.
It went away.
No, it didn't. It's close.
It's merely attempting to determine
the perfect shooting angle.
You're wrong.
It went to chase him.
The boy on the other side of this door.
It's trying to kill the boy who
told us about the secret passageway.
Jolene, take cover.
I came here today to help
you get out of this place.
Before I came to this room,
that boy, he grabbed
my arm as I walked by.
He did.
As strange as it may seem, he's here.
Just an ordinary kid like
you'd see in the park,
and a total stranger to me
for whatever it's worth.
And yet, he grabbed me
as if he depended on me.
It was strangely soothing, the
warmth of his hand holding my arm.
That's why I'm going back in.
I'm going to defeat Jean Gloria
before he shoots that poor kid.
Good grief.
Check visitation!
The fire alarm is coming from there!
I don't know the situation because
there's no car in that room!
Where?
Where did he go?
That boy.
Where the hell did he come from?
And how was he able to
just disappear like that?
Hurry! It's room B!
Did he dig this hole? In this wall?
He must have gone in here.
This one's height is roughly
four and a half feet tall.
He's small, like a child.
I don't know who he is, but the
hole that suddenly opened is a vent.
I can tell right where it leads
by the movement of the wind.
But still,
I must do everything in my power to
prevent that little guy from guiding
Jotaro and Jolene to the vent where my
bullets have no hope of reaching them.
I will not lose sight of them any longer.
I'll shoot down that little brat first.
Jolene the situation has gotten too heavy
now the stand can only be used for defense
if we try to attack it it will
detect the change in airflow
it's way too heavy
hey you you aren't allowed to leave
visitation this is the prison side
what the
that thing is here too
it really is hunting for that kid
but how does he plan to
shoot a bullet from the
men's prison into a utility
room that has no windows
What?
Hold on Is he?
That hatch
Clever.
Nice work, kid.
I just hope you're as
lucky as you are smart.
If his entire body is in the
water, there are no air currents.
Especially inside the pipe.
Looks like it already
lost sight of him, too.
And there aren't any windows in this room.
There's no way he can shoot me.
The pipe.
But why?
And from where?
You're kidding!
Distance 321 meters.
The bullet drops 9.5
centimeters in transit.
Wind speed of 3.2 meters from the right.
This shifts the bullet
4.2 centimeters left.
Target identified.
Point of aim is locked
on his heart. Watch out!
Stone Ocean!
Those threads, it's Jolene Kujo.
I clearly recognize her stand.
She's just jumped out of cover.
Is she an idiot?
You really think that will save you?
Shifting point of aim to Jolene.
Headshot lined up.
Now say cheese!
Hmph.
What?
Well, look at that.
Glad I broke that pipe earlier.
When I busted the pipe coming in
here, I remembered some basic science.
Gas is lightweight,
so when it accumulates
around a given area,
it can create a completely
separate airflow.
Which would put you at a disadvantage
reading the air currents guess I was right
What did you do?
Seems like John Gloria
couldn't read his own luck
Hey, who are you?
And how the hell is a little kid like you
able to move freely around this prison?
That hurt.
This thing.
That's right, you gave this to me earlier.
What is this?
Looks like some kind of bone.
Why did you hand this to me?
You told me not to go
to the visiting room.
How do you know so much about me?
I want an answer!
In time, things will be revealed.
Just hold on to what I
gave you, no matter what.
The smell.
Is that your doing?
I captured Jean Gallier's sniper stand.
It wasn't so tough when
I had it in my net.
And so, I smashed it to pieces. I see.
It would appear you've already grown
accustomed to fighting using your stand.
It's not like I wanted to.
He's in here! Behind that!
I just saw him moving!
Hide!
He has a rifle!
He's up there behind that pipe!
He crawled up above that tank!
That would be impossible he fired
from the men's prison which is two
to three hundred meters away add in
dozens of steel bars and the fact
that the man is almost blind how in
the world would he have been able
to get here so quick no idea but
I saw him in here with us get down
he's in the crawlspace above
you very well I trust you Hoorah!
Prepare yourself.
Sure enough, gas is accumulated by now.
We did it!
Hey, the coast is clear now!
Huh? What?
The kid.
Where'd he go?
Hey!
You can come out!
We took care of the bad guy!
Come out and tell me what's going on!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm looking for the kid!
Did you happen to see which
way the little boy went?
I don't understand what you're asking.
Who's this boy you're talking about?
There was this kid.
How could you not see
him in his baseball gear?
That's who I was talking to when
we were in the visiting room.
It was this boy.
John Gloria was even trying to kill
this kid for getting in his way.
Kill him?
Seriously I don't know
what you're talking about
you came all the way down
to this room on your own.
That's why I decided to follow you down.
Hang on that doesn't make
any sense you should have
heard the boy's voice at least
there's no way you wouldn't
have heard him I mean he's
the one who told us about
the secret passage in the
first place we talked about it
remember did you hear a
ghost talking I don't know
anything about secret passageways
damn it old man why are
you trying to mess with my
head at a time like this you
came here through that secret
passageway just like I did
Wait a second something about you
just seems off your wound what the
hell happened to that bullet wound
you had a wound John Gloria shot
you in your left shoulder I saw
it and yet your arm isn't bleeding
at all what mine too my gunshot
wound just disappeared and who is this
that isn't John Gloria it's
one of the guards but I
thought he'd been shot in
the head in the visiting room
no sign of a wound at all
what gunshots are you talking
about who the devil What the
hell is this John Gloria?
What the hell is happening?
This can't be right.
It doesn't make any sense.
What the hell is going on?
I know that's something even more
unfortunate than death will occur.
No matter what, you absolutely
cannot go to the visiting room.
The visiting room. That's right.
It was odd right from the start.
My handcuffs.
When did they disappear?
And that bullet. I'd been shot.
But did any of that really happen?
Neither myself nor Dad are even wounded.
Did Jean Gloria even attack us?
I can't keep things straight anymore.
How strange.
None of this makes any sense.
This isn't reality.
I must be hallucinating.
Or else.
It's someone else's doing.
No way.
Stop it.
A dream was that all a dream
but when did I start dreaming?
Looks like I really did beat up that
guard though I guess that's real.
This is a photo of John Gloria that's the
same one that dad showed
me he told me about.
The accident with the hitchhiker how John
Gloria set it all up
back then that's real.
After that, I got up and
tried to leave this room.
That's when I realized
my handcuffs were gone.
Ever since then.
No.
If we're still sitting at this
table, it happened before that.
I haven't stepped foot out of the
visiting room since I got here.
That means...
My mind made it all up?
Jean Gallier's stand?
And all that bullshit about air currents?
The secret passageway and what followed.
From the moment we stepped into this
visitation room, we fell into a trap.
And I've been hallucinating ever since.
Slowly but surely, as if we were
sitting in a huge snake's stomach,
we were melting away.
The boy hiding in the trash
can who gave me this bone.
He's real!
I woke up from this nightmare
because I hurt my hand on this bone.
Without this sharp pain, I would
have stayed asleep and died!
This power of illusions.
This must be Zhang Kali's actual stand!
My thread.
I can't keep it together.
Oh, shit.
Damn it.
I'm tired, but I can't go to sleep again.
No way.
I'm not going out like this.
We have to escape from this goddamn room!
Stone Ocean!
Although you think I cope.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place.
Other than he.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.